Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the Tim
Dylan Show.
Fair is fair.
We must,
even though we are cautious
about what this guy does, a lot to not
like,
some things to like.
We want to congratulate
the mayor
of
the I'm sorry, the the mayoral
candidate
for the Democratic Party
in
New York City
and his name
is Osama bin Laden.
I want to congratulate him.
I
thought
it was an ambitious
thing
to have attacked the financial capital
of the world to have hid out and to come
back
and to have noticed how much salads
cost, sandwiches, just lunch in general,
how angry people were and to come in and
go, "Listen, I know I did wrong with the
Twin Towers.
I know I it it wasn't ideal, but
remember what you were paying for rent
when I attacked the World Trade Center?
How much more equitable it was? How
much? Remember in 2001
when 20 bucks
bought you a pack of smokes, a cocktail,
a dime bag of weed, and a burrito and
that's your night
when I attack the World Trade Center.
And he would say he would say in the
speeches he gojustifiably
many would clap. Yes, we agree. I
attacked it justifiably
because of the things I didn't agree
with, troops in Saudi Arabia,
America's support for Israel.
But even as I watched people jump out of
those buildings to their sudden and uh
inevitable death, I thought to myself,
maybe I'll come back here one day and
give them free buses.
So when Osama bin Laden came back to the
city
to give people
a more
equitable
plan to live.
I I I get it.
I get it. Hey, I'm not dead. The Navy
Seals didn't get me. And I'm here to
make buses free.
government-run grocery stores. Let's get
rid of the cops. Let's get people
walking around with clipboards
asking questions.
Of course, I am kidding. Osama bin Laden
is is not the nominee.
Osama bin Laden was a CIA asset that we
pretended lived in Pakistan. And then we
sent a group of Navy Seals to kill him
who are they also somehow died in a
mission which seems odd but they're all
dead. Like I think all the members of
Seal Team Six are dead. Don't look it
up. It doesn't matter. But go I believe
that to be the case truly. And it was
very weirdly like we kind of knew
Pakistan had him and we didn't. Uh
listen, let's not get lost in that.
My point is that Osama bin Laden,
wherever he is,
uh, is not the guy. I know that Charlie
Kirk, a few people have made that kind
of comparison.
There's a lot about 911 we don't know.
So, I don't think we can. And listen, by
the way, I'm no fan of the uh,
immigration. I'd like it to uh, cool
down.
I'm a big fan of a cool down with the
immigration. A cooling period, a cooling
off period, a settling in. How about
that? A settling in. No one talks about
immigration like that. Let's let all
these immigrants settle in. If you ever
stayed at someone's house and they go,
"Let me let you get settled.
That's what we want."
But so this is not a defense of radical
Islam or immigration. Two things I'm no
fan of.
There's a lot more to 9/11 than just,
hey,
you know, couple of guys in a cave
didn't like us. Now, I don't know how
much more there is to it,
but if you have uh an education level
beyond uh fifth grade, you realize
something else
is a foot.
This seems to be one of the biggest
issues with the Republican party right
now is they are unable to
when they try to dunk on a guy like
uh Zoron Mama who is the uh
Democratic primary winner. Zoran mama,
they don't understand when when they
just say the word 911, it's bad for them
because everything after 9/11
was terrible.
And that's why we all look at the Iran
engagement and go, let's relax.
Let's calm it down.
War gives people something to do in the
government.
People think the government does more
than it does and it doesn't do all of
that that much and there's a lot of
people that don't do that much. But when
there's a war like everyone's working
like we've talked about it on this show
when the Pentagon like when they're
about to go to war they all start
ordering pizzas. It's like they have
something called the pizza index where
people know when we may or may not go to
war or drop a bomb because everyone at
the Pentagon's like staying late and
ordering pizza because they have to
work. It gives them purpose. Tonight's
the night. We got to do it. It's time.
Get the You know what I mean? And
they're and they're going Pepperoni
and and we'll hit it and we'll hold on.
Yeah. If they come with it, fine. If the
wings come with it, fine. I don't want.
Is it a deal?
No. They'll pierce underground 30 to 50
ft. And we're hoping the rubble will go
on top of it. So even if we don't
destroy it, they're not going to be able
to get the nuclear. Hold on one second.
I apologize. If it's a deal, yes. If
we're paying extra, then no. I don't
know how many ways to say it. If it cut,
then get the deal. The deal is two
pizzas. Well, then take take half of one
home.
Take half of one home. Hold on.
Someone's calling. Oh, it's the vice
president. It doesn't It's not a big
deal. Don't answer. Take the
We kid Vance, who I believe is still
working for the government. Do we know
that? I don't know. It seems like he
might be. He's kind of working for the
government.
Get up the thing. get up JD Vince on Fox
News with the Iran deal where where
Mullen sent this to me where he was like
um he's like that's not the draft. He's
like that's not the draft I saw but uh
he goes what I like about the president
is he's always working.
Yeah. I mean, he does a he does a thing
where he's talking about the deal and uh
that the this draft of this deal thing
that happened and he goes on Fox and
he's like, "Well, the language was a
little different from the draft that I
saw, but what I love about the president
is he's always working. He's always
that guy does not stop working."
Um, you know, he and this is it's just
fun. It's like, you know, I imagine he's
involved tangentially
with some of it. I don't I don't you
know, who can know over there who's in
and who's out. I think they've got Tulsi
Gabbard doing tough mutter races. I
don't think she's allowed in the
building. I can I don't know.
The Hills are Tim Dylan attacks Tulsi
Gabbard. I didn't attack her. I like
Tulsi Gabbard. I said, if all these dark
forces are are are goating us in a war,
can you mention a few of their names?
you know, a few of their names might be
good has just put out in this
administration. Brett, it happens quite
a bit actually, but we knew this was
coming. Um, the the draft, it was
interesting. I just read the draft about
2 minutes before we went on the air. It
was a little bit different from what the
president had showed me a couple of
hours ago, but again, I knew that he was
working the phones as I was on the way
over here. So, I knew exactly what we
were going to do. And and look, I I I
love that about this presidency and this
administration is he's always working.
He doesn't say, you know, the vice
president's going to do an interview, so
I'm going to stop doing anything. He
says, you know, we're going to do the
American people's business. The vice
president, he's like, it's not like the
vice president is doing an interview
with me. I'm I'm going to stop doing it
or tell them what we're doing. I'm just
going to let see what happens out there.
See if he can uh, you know, run
interference. Just stall,
you know, hold them, as we'd say. The
headliner is not here. You go out there
and hold them. keep them keep them
going. So I think JD Vance is still
working there. I'm unsure. I don't know.
But the thing that Republicans don't
realize when they go after this Zoron
Mama Mam Dani
who is a
young, you know, like attractive,
energetic person who's got some wacky
ideas about like free grocery stores and
free bus rides. I mean, if you were
homeless, wouldn't you just go to the
hang out on the bus if it was free? I
would. I don't take buses. You I don't
care what happens to them. But I imagine
there are people that do take them and
they wouldn't they don't want just
homeless people on the buses and people
selling drugs on the buses and and
[__] people on the buses. But that's
what I would do if it was all free and I
was homeless. I'd go, "Well, why
wouldn't I just get on a bus?"
But he's going to have the grocery
stores because of the price of food. and
he's going to instead of police when
someone lights someone on fire on a
subway, he's going to send like a a team
of mental health professionals to ask
that person to stop and to deescalate
the situation because in his mind and in
the mind of many people, the
deescalation
uh is going to be done like with a with
a compassion and like having like an
intellectual
game plan going into it when there's
like a guy who's like screaming and you
know, you're going to be like, "All
right, how do we get to him?
Like, how do we Jedi mind read where
he's at?" And it's going to be
interesting and exciting to see what
happens with that. I do think you need
the threat of lethal force in a lot of
cases. Not all of them, but it does seem
like
if there's a guy and he's about to light
a woman on fire, it's kind of
interesting being like, "Wait, hey,
where's this coming from? Like, where's
this coming from? Why are you doing
this? What is this going to solve?
Really?
Don't you understand
that by lighting this innocent woman on
fire?
You know, you're just
you're putting yourself into a position
you don't want to be.
And it seems to me that you're in pain
and you're hurting. And I understand
that. A lot of things about society
don't make any sense, right? I mean, all
these apartments, all these rich guys
live in them, but they don't even live
there. like they barely live there. They
use these
apartment buildings as vertical money
laundering units and they launder money
from all over the world and they don't
pay any taxes and the working class
bears the brunt of this because their
jobs are shipped overseas and their
standard of living drops. I understand
where your rage comes from. And then at
this point, the guys are
and they go, I that guttural yell
is we understand where it comes from.
It's a lack of health care, the respect
that women aren't given, how much harder
it is for trans people of color. And the
guy's like, but then he starts to like
then they walk over, they start petting
him. He puts the gas can down and they
go, "We we know
and they go, we know how difficult it is
to exist in a society like that.
So, let us take you to this
governmentowned grocery store. Would you
like to go to the government-owned
grocery store?
They have a lot of nice They have little
hummus cups. And the thing about hummus,
and there'll be a a Jewish girl with big
glasses, and she'll go, "And the thing
about hummus is if you eat too much, I
get gassy." But these little hummus cups
are like perfectly portioned. And the
guy will go
and then he'll be like shirtless. He's
covered in blood. And then he's got he
puts a gas can down. And then they walk
him out. And then they bring him to the
government grocery store. and they
started talking to him about and then
they'll find out the whole thing was a
gluten allergy that his he was not
metabolizing gluten and that's one of
the reasons he was going to uh light
that woman on fire on the subway
and if that works it work I hope it
works by the way count me in I'd like it
to work I'm no fan of the cops I was
pulled over going 97 out to Southampton
[__] you I'll never do a fundraiser for
you scum stay with the fire department
never see me wearing an NYPD Not even
though they don't really bother me, but
just the Long Island Trooper, New York
State Troopers. [__] you. Not for me. It
is what it is. They got me going 97
or 87, whatever. 87.
It's not right. They see the Bentley.
It's class warfare. Everyone's speeding.
Everyone's going fast. They pull me over
because they're like, "Fuck this guy."
Then they pull me over. They're like,
"Where do you even live?" I go, "Who
knows?"
They go, "Where's this car registered?"
I go, "I don't I think Beverly Hills,
buddy. Just write the ticket, you slob."
So, I'm not cucking
for the cops.
I'm just saying it might be interesting
because I I think you know if we look at
San Francisco and a few of these other
cities, Portland, Seattle, Detroit,
Chicago, the Democrats who've run these
cities
haven't produced great things. But I
don't know, maybe it won't go that way
where it's like flash mobs of children.
I mean, Chicago's just fully got flash
mobs of teenagers
storming
places. If ED is getting you down, you
need HIMS to help your confidence, among
other things. Hims provides access to
treatments that can help you stay hard
and last longer. You can be ready
whenever the mood strikes. Feeling a
little sold out in the bedroom? Through
HIMS, you can get some gas back in the
tank with personalized ED treatments
that are accessible without ever
stepping foot into a doctor's office.
For men dealing with ED can be
uncomfortable, which is why HIMS
provides access to an to a comfortable
solution with all online process and
personalized treatment options. HIMS is
changing men's healthcare by providing
you with access to affordable sexual
health treatments from the comfort of
your couch. Start your free online visit
today at hms.com/tim. That's hs.com
for your personalized ED treatment
options. hymns.comtim.
A featured the featured products include
compounded products which are not
approved or verified by the safety
effectiveness or quality by the FDA.
Prescription required. See website for
details. Restrictions and important
safety information. Price varies based
on product and subscription plan. But
hey,
I wish Zoran
and he wants to tax richer and whiter
people. He won over everybody making
over $100,000 a year voted for the guy.
And here's one of the reasons obviously
um he is appealing to
a demographic of people who
are understandably and understand what
I'm saying here because you're not
wrong. Understandably frustrated that
their level of education has not turned
into income.
Understand what I'm saying here? I say
the most valuable things in the world,
by the way. Actually, in between, oh,
that was a really funny bit.
Yeah, we gota But now I'm gonna say
something actually brilliant. That's
actually the right thing always.
Okay,
Diddy's innocent though. But they just
wrapped Diddy's uh defense.
Zoran Mandami
Mamani
M
Zoran Zoran don't mess with the Zoron
right Zohan what was it don't start with
me folks
they are angry that he's appealing to a
constituency of people who are angry
that their income
that their education is not reflected in
their income
and these people were told their entire
life that all they had to do to make
money was to get a college degree.
This is a generation of people
that were told that the route to comfort
and security was education.
And all of those people then graduated
from schools in an alarming amount of
debt.
They were also told they should follow
their passions in life and work in a
field that was interesting, exciting and
maybe creative adjacent.
So lots of these people move to cities
to get jobs
in finance, tech, media,
whatever.
And a lot of companies over the last few
years have hemorrhaged jobs.
Specifically people in the media sphere.
Yeah. And the entertainment world. Okay.
But many other industries as well.
The constituency that's powering Mani's
campaign is by the numbers a
higher educated higher income
group. But they're not high income
compared to new compared to what you
would need to feel rich in New York. I
don't feel rich in New York. And I make
a hell of a lot more money than these
zeros.
Now,
it doesn't
mean that Mandani is wrong about wealth
inequality in America and specifically
in New York. He's correct about that.
It's the same
It's the same issue that Donald Trump
built a coalition around.
Fairness.
Trump's coalition focused obviously more
on immigration.
Um, a populist nationalist
uprising against elites in education,
media, wherever. Mamani has a similar
thing. It's a populist uprising,
but instead of being directed at the
elites in media and entertainment,
because the they largely, many of them
are supporting him. Not the big elites,
not the billionaires, not my Metal Lane
boys and girls. Shout out to the whole
crowd. Buy me, daddy. I'm here. Human
shields. Say no more. But shell out a
little. No. Shell out.
Um,
can't defend everything for free. You'd
give me money. I'll pop right on here.
I'll pop right on here. Here's an L.
Here's an L. But you got to give me a
little. Give me a little.
Give me a What about a basket? You send
a basket over. Couple of Goldberg's
bagels, some locks, some scallion cream
cheese.
Just a little gesture. I'm not asking
for a ABC.
What I'm saying is the the big boys and
girls, the big institutional money
doesn't like the guy, but the rank and
file in the media and entertainment kind
of like him. So, their populist rage is
not directed
that way.
They also don't have a problem with the
trans stuff in the schools and whatnot.
Their rage is directed at rich people
and white people
and Jewish people, but not really for
the not and and let me be careful how I
say this, but not for the principled
reason. Yes, it was, as Bannon said, a
referendum on Netanyahu and Israel's a
failed war in Gaza. Now, obviously,
Israel would say it's done very well
because they've gotten rid of a lot of
Hamas, but failed, meaning that it's
it's it's further inflamed sentiment
against not only Israel, but Jews living
all over the world because of what most
people are seeing as going way, way, way
overboard. And that's the nicest way to
say it. But the the reason a lot of
people in the Mamani camp
are putting Jews, it's the colonizer
narrative
that applies in their head across the
board to any white settler colonial
project,
America, UK, France, Israel. In this way
that you look at the world, any violence
done by any group that is a little more
tan is usually justifiable and ignored
or even the Chinese there's no real
there's no there's no real like passion
for like the weaguers who were in some
camp. And I'm not even saying there
should be per se. Like I'm just saying
if we're going to start litigating
history, they ignore before like 18th
19th century colonialism, they ignore a
lot of
other colonial projects,
anything in the Far East, anything that
the Muslims have done wrong. This isn't
something that they love talking about,
but it's populism nonetheless.
This is why when Mandani said he wants
to shift the tax burden to richer and
whiter neighborhoods if he secures the
election in November, a housing policy
document on Mamani's official website
includes a pledge to shift the tax
burden from overtaxed homeowners in the
outer burrows to more expensive homes in
richer and whiter neighborhoods. It is
about
grievance, racial grievance.
It's what it is. And it's it's it's it's
kind of undeniable if that's how you
present it. He's not wrong that the cost
of living in New York City is insane.
He's not wrong that people not having
health care, people working overtime. I
I I'm with him on all that and I'm with
a lot of people on on on on the far left
on that those issues and the far right.
Why you would include whiter in that
sentence would is insane to me. Why you
keep racializing
this debate about inequality. They they
they
s they can't avoid it.
This is why everybody freaked out about
racial humor during the uh 2020 uh
insanity was because these people, a lot
of the people that supported Zoron, a
lot of them have never worked shitty
jobs and they've never they were never
in a situation where they're kidding
around with people and they're all
making fun of each other because of
their race. And it's not a big deal.
It's actually people bond over it. These
people have only worked in corporate
America or they've only been to college.
They don't they're not really thrust
into these environments where racial
humor is actually not not only is it not
a negative, a lot of times it's a
positive. It's a the way people bond.
So if you run AOC, you'll lose because
she can't detach
populism from racial grievance.
The Democrats are having a hard time
doing that. And one of the reasons that
they're having a hard time doing it is
it's just hardwired into them. The
identity is hardwired into them. But he
won and he won because it is the message
is
a salient point. Things aren't fair.
People cannot live.
And the Republicans should take a note.
Andrew Cuomo's up there looking like a
guy who runs a diner in Carl Place, Long
Island,
stammering,
trying to defend himself against, I
don't know, 13 women who he like, you
know, gooseed while they were online for
[__] Chicken Franches at the
Christmas party. He looks old and out of
touch. He's talking about going to
Israel as soon as he takes the oath of
office. He's going to take it on a plane
on LL on the way to Israel. It doesn't
look good. Read the room.
Read the room a little bit. People that
are broke in New York are concerned
about New York,
you know.
So, the coalition there
and it's not black people. They voted
largely for Cuomo. And here's in my
estimation why
there is no group of people in America
who who who are owed more than black
people and have gotten less. There's not
one group. We've spent the last few
years talking about Latinos who have now
passed black people as a voting block
and an economic block. We now talk only
about immigrants coming from other
countries. We speak um about Jews and
Muslims frankly more than Americanborn
black people. They know
that
the conversation
has moved on from them. Mandani is
talking about immigrants
more than black people.
They know that they're not stupid.
They're well aware that the Democratic
Party's kind of moved on a little bit
from black people. They get it. They get
it. They're going, "Yeah, yeah, yeah. We
get we pick up what you're putting
down." So, I think Cuomo to them has
name recognition and they're, you know,
they're they understand
that this is going in the direction that
doesn't include them. The Democrats are
building a a coalition that doesn't
include black people. They know it.
They're well aware of it. It's it's it's
it's it's coastal
uh educated, college educated. I'm not
saying smart. I'm saying educated white
people and illegal immigrants.
That's all. That's their coalition. It's
not the worst coalition.
There's nothing wrong with with that,
but it does include black people. It's
it's it's people in the GBTQ
IA2
world.
Um, it's it's educated white people and
it's it's it's it's immigrants
that that's primarily the Democratic
coalition. That's all they're talking
about ever. They they talk about
low-income people. But I mean, it's like
eh, but it's it's really the cultural
energies behind immigration.
And Zoron's like, we're going to Trump
proof New York because he might cut our
federal funding. And listen, I'm an
opponent of those barbaric ICE raids. I
think they're [__] up. But I do think
criminals need to be deported. And I
also think criminals will have wives and
kids.
So a guy that's wanted for attempted mur
when everyone goes, "Oh, that woman's
pregnant. They went to her house." It's
like a pregnant mother, yes, but her
husband was wanted for attempted murder.
So there are going to be situations
where shockingly
murderers and people that have been
violent have also procreated and that,
you know, so it's just going to be a
situation
where it's like, "But he's a father."
It's like, "Yeah, okay.
You know who's a father? Putin.
Putin's a father.
It's so important right now to have good
credit. It can save you anything. Car
loans, mortgage,
apartments, gas prices up, rent up, way
up, groceries. Don't even get me
started. It c feels like everything
costs more except credit building with
kickoff. At a time when money's tighter
than ever, kickoff gives you an
affordable way to build real credit
without the stress of expensive credit
card debt. No credit check, no interest,
just $5 a month. And it can really help
move your score up fast.
I built my credit years ago and I wish I
had kickoff.
So many of my friends are using kickoff.
Users with credit under 600 grew an
average of 84 points in their first year
with on-time payments with transparent
affordable plans starting at $5 a month.
No hidden fees and zero interest.
Kickoff helps you score big when it
comes to credit. It's simple. You make
on-time payments, credit bureaus see
good behavior and your credit can grow
fast.
Start building credit immediately for
only $1 your first month. And by the
way, it's not you don't even have to
have horrible credit to utilize this.
Any credit score can be improved with
kickoff. The autopay feature helps you
build credit while you sleep, and you
never worry about missing a payment.
Stop building your credit, little dirt
bag. Start building your credit, little
pig.
Start building your credit, little dirt
bag. Getkickoff.com/tim
getkickoff k i kofffff.com
today. That's get kickoff kofff.com.
Start building your credit with kickoff
today and you could get your first month
for as little as $1. That's 80% off the
normal price when you go to
getkickoff.com/tim
today. Get kickoff you little [__]
dirt bag. Must sign up via get
kickoff.com/tim to activate offer offer
plus a new kickoff customers first month
only subject to approval offer subject
to change. Average first year credit
score impact of plus 84 points manage
score 3.0 between January 2023 and
January 2024 for kickoff credit account
users who start with a score below 600
who paid on time and who have no
delinquencies or collections added to
their credit profile during that period.
Late payments may negatively impact your
credit score. Individual results may
vary.
So I So by the way, good luck to Zoran.
Let's get the sandwich article up
because I get it. The rage. I've lived
in New York on and off. Not enough to
pay taxes here, but on and off for a
while, and I've seen it only get more
expensive and more boring and more
corporate.
Um, now I'm not saying I long for the
days of Dangerous New York, cuz by the
way, I was like nine. Most people who
want that New York back never lived in
it at all. They're all nostalgic for a
time that you know that was back when
like a Rocket would have a knife in her
back in in Central Park. That was a big
story. There was a Rock Cat
with a knife in her back in the park and
it was on the cover like the Daily News
and stuff and people were like maybe
it's time to start cleaning this up. And
then Giuliani came in because it was
getting hairy out there. That was that
kind of New York and you'd be walking in
the park, jogging, whatever, and there'd
just be a rocket with a butcher knife
sticking out of her back
and a lot of pe So that was the old New
York, you know, and
sure it was, you know, if you visited
New York and saw that you got you had a
story. It was a better story than, hey,
do you know how uh crowded the raising
canes in Time Square were? I'll give you
that. Here's what I will give you.
Visiting New York and saying I got blown
in the bathroom of CBGB
by someone I didn't know if they were a
man or a woman. And then I woke up in an
apartment I'd never been in before. I
went on the roof. I smoked a cigarette
uh with some chick who talked about
Buddhism. Then I went down to take a
walk in the park to clear my head and I
saw a girl with a butcher knife hanging
out of her back who was very very long
legs. Turned out she was a rockette. One
of the rockets. Cuz this girl with the
butcher knife was a rocket. And that's a
real story that someone would have told
and has told who visited New York. Now
the stories in New York are like, "Yeah,
there's a race in Canes in Time Square
and it's too crowded." So we didn't get
it. We didn't get it because there was
so there were a lot of people in it and
because we didn't get it. So we then
went to see uh a Broadway show. We got
Yeah. So we got tickets to the Trish Pis
uh musical review and but we couldn't
and we wanted to do a Raising Kane's
mukbang and tag her because she likes
chicken fingers but we couldn't do it.
And then our flight at Newark airport
was delayed like 4 hours and it was
crazy. So I just sat there and went on
my phone and I scrolled through apps and
I just looked at people's faces and I
wondered if they felt anything cuz I
didn't. And I wondered what would make
me feel. And then for a brief moment I
thought I looked at these big beautiful
planes through the glass windows of
Newark airport and I wondered what would
it feel like if one of them instead of
landing on the runway just crashed in
here and everyone started screaming and
yelling and the last thing I saw was the
fire. Would I feel the fuel as it burned
my skin? What would it feel like to die?
Would I know I was dying? Would I die
and go somewhere else? Would people I
know be there like my friends and my
family? What will happen? And what was
the meaning of all of this? Why am I
dying? Because I want Is it because I
didn't go to Raising Canes? Should I
have stayed on the line? Is it a weird
final destination because I didn't eat
the chicken finger? And just as I was
having that thought, they said the plane
was boarding and the flight was easy, no
turbulence. We landed in Phoenix at
11:06.
What I'm saying is it's kind of bland
now. Somewhat boring. Predictable.
Predictable.
We've created a world where no one
feels. Politics is the only thing that
makes them feel. How terrible. What a
bad idea.
Politics is the only thing that makes
people feel anymore. People can't People
there. No one's [__] the way that
they should be in a messy, gross,
kind of sloppy way. It's all very
prefuncter,
strange, specific [__] because porn's
so specific where it's like someone's
like, I can only come if I'm looking at
a plant or some, you know, it's like it
nothing. Everybody's trying every the
perfect has become the enemy of the
good. Oh my god. Say it again. The
good. Everyone wants to just [__]
genderless weird strange Scandinavian
furniture. People are afraid of rashes
and boils and you know weird hair and
places and everybody wants women to look
like these egirl types and like in the
70s people would just [__] and they they
were on an old carpet and just a you
know you know what I mean? Like people
would [__] in a cab. There'd just be an
Arab guy silently driving on the West
Side Highway. But now it's all people on
these weird dates and talk about
nothing. So my sister is basically like
dating this guy for like 3 years, but
then like we're like where's it going?
They go on vacation all the time. It's
like where you think he proposed.
There's like 90 places like me and my
girlfriend's like, "Oh my god, is this a
place?" Cuz they go everywhere and
there's like 90 places he could have
pulled out a ring, but he like never
has. And we're like, "Maybe he's not
even planning to." And she's like, "I'm
letting him go at his own pace." And I'm
like, "Well, actually, that's like nice
of you to say, but like how do you even
know he's going to do it?" And then we
and this is people just it's it's all
nothing out there. So that's why people
get excited about politics because they
say, "Here's our chance to make other
people feel pain."
That's what drives politics, not helping
other people. Not in this country, by
the way. Not in this country. It should
and it does in certain certain ways. But
the reality is you want other people to
feel pain. Both the left and the right
want other people to feel pain. That's
what that is the political impulse. Tuck
them. Get them. Kill them.
That's what it is. And people are doing
that because they they can't feel any
everything in life that was supposed to
make them feel things. sex, family,
success, money. It's It's all been
ruined to a degree. It's all been
sanitized
and made kind of uh unappealing to
people. Like, it certainly doesn't equal
the fun, raw, direct hit of rage and
anger. That's more fun than like
building something slowly over time that
might be valuable in your life. It's
never going to be as fun as [__] him,
kill him, kill him, [__] him, kill him,
kill him. You like that, mom? The Muslim
one. You like that, mom? You like it,
mom?
It's the rage. It's just the same way
when Trump won, all those people called
their kids. He's back in town. The
sheriff's back in town.
It's the rage
that keeps people going because we've
made the world
corporate
serene. I mean, not serene if you're
obviously getting bombed, but like for a
lot of these types, these college
educated people that live in little
boxes all over these cities that scroll
dating apps and just sit in the blue
light of their MacBook while they drift
off to sleep on 19 medications.
These people's lives are quite dull
and the only thing that is making them
happy is rage
and that's okay. I don't I'm not I'm not
saying this is good or bad. It seems
like a a horrible way to live long term
and it seems like we'll just degenerate
into kind of meaningless sporadic bouts
of violence that will be celebrated by
different groups. We will glorify uh
violence. Um demand your own thing.
Nobody feels bad for the healthcare CEO,
nor really should they in the sense that
he represents an evil to people. My
mother died in a public institution. I
get it. They wouldn't pay for her [__]
I would go in and have to sue them to
give her the accurate amount of
medication because they wouldn't. They
wanted to save money and let her go
crazier because it's a profit-driven
system and it's evil. And he was a
representative of that. Was he a human
being? Yes. Is it a healthy society that
celebrates a human being shot uh dead in
the street? And I mean, this is
disgusting. And I usually don't even
talk like this. And I don't ever go with
comedians. Literally, I never go
comedians on the show because I respect
comedy. I don't know who it was. A
comedian
dressed up as the ghost of that
healthcare CEO
a few weeks after he died
and went on a roast and did jokes. That
guy has a family. Do you understand
that?
It is immoral
to behave like this for not even a lot
of money. Almost no money actually
because I know a little bit about that.
almost no money.
But it's sick. It's actually sick.
Whoever did that,
it was a successful comedian,
a good-looking comedian, at least
facially.
And it was wrong what that person did
because they didn't have to do it. That
comedian actually didn't have to do
something like that. He's actually
incredibly rich and successful, smart,
one of the smartest people in the world.
People say, "Actually, why would that
person do that?" Because there's the
moral code's gone. The compass is over.
So, there's a sick person on Torching
2024, The Rose of Netflix,
um, who dressed up as Brian Thompson,
the the CEO. It's wrong. Whoever did
that, I don't know.
I just think that
I'm interested to see what happens with
this guy. I'm not interested like I
don't left right like all this shit's
bor it's boring. We all know what it is.
Everybody gets in America first and then
they're in there.
It's whatever. It's fine. It's fine.
What are you gonna do is what it is.
Everybody's as long as everybody's
happy.
Do I think it's a good idea to go, you
know, to start building schools in Iran?
No. But that's good. We just did a bomb.
Did it get rid of the thing? Who gives a
[__] Probably kind of. What do you care
about? Enough. Take the win.
But it it it's it's just about you know
what it is. It's just about to me what
what what says more about the the
political stuff is what's behind it. You
have these people that are all like
they went to school. They were told they
were very special people and talented
and they got into the right schools and
got the right degrees and now they're
like paying $29 for a sandwich in New
York City and they're pissed. They got
to take [__] from some boss. And New
York makes you envious like no place.
And by the way, I'm not talking about
the people who genuinely need help in
this city, okay? the black people that
the Democratic Party don't give a [__]
about whose lives
uh a lot of them are fully responsible
for the degradation of African-American
communities
um
and
do deserve a lot more than the
government does.
I'm not talking about those people and
I'm not talking about the people that
suffer under a health care system. I'm
talking about now people that are
envious
as I am. I'm an envious. We all envy.
And the people that don't admit it are
liars.
I envy people. I do my podcast in a
building with a lot of finance people
and I understand. And they make more
money than me. Why
would that be the case? Because we live
in a sick society.
But
that
envy,
New York City breeds it
because the richest people in the world
live here.
The richest, wealthiest people, and I
don't mean only in America, all over the
world live here.
People talk [__] to you here and down to
you in accents from all over the globe.
You get insulted here in different
languages
because it's a global city.
I think that restoring the balance will
be good. If he can make this city more
affordable, it can be good. If he turns
it into a crimeridden hellscape, not
great. Not great. If he's blaming Whitey
and the Jews for everything, not great.
I don't love that. I don't love making
it a sanctuary for third world
illegal labor that billionaires can use
instead of nativeborn people. And I
don't want to talk about uh Jews and
Muslims for the rest of my life. There
are Christians who live in America that
should hold some political office, too.
Sorry. No offense. No offense. I know
that all the signers of the Declaration
of Independence were Jewish and Muslim,
right? I mean, Google that. Maybe they
weren't. But the point is this. I I I
think the conversation is too dominant.
Oh, I love Jewish people. I have great
Jew Muslim friends. I love the whole
desert. All of the desert people, the
desert tribes, actually. All of the
desert tribes. I like I like their food.
I bought a schwarma, a lamb schwarma for
my friend before we came here. It's why
I'm late.
I love all the desert tribal peoples.
Yes, they're fighting religious wars all
the time. Is it tiring? For me, it is.
But I do think how about how about just
a few
Christian people who've lived in America
for a few generations.
Just throwing it out there as a bit as a
full bit.
But again, might be interesting.
That's all because it's too much. I even
think the Jews and the Mus are sick of
being discussed as much as we talk about
and we're just talk. It's too much
already.
It's too much. I America shouldn't just
be a place where people where these
groups of people are just waring all the
time and fighting all the time. It's
like
we have to
return to a little bit of concern
for the United States as a country, as a
nation, as something that should be
functional. Society has to return to
being functional.
Okay? It it can't be an algorithm-driven
cash grab for insane grifters who have
Palunteer tattooed on their ass. We need
some type of functionality. Everyone who
visits my homes, whether it's in Aspen
or the Hamptons or Palm Beach,
Manhattan, Beverly Hills, Paris, London,
St. Kits, the Moldes, St. Bar, St. Croy,
St. Lucia, Little St. James, Tuscanyany,
Boston, Chicago, Miami, Scottdale,
Arizona,
Summerland, Nevada,
uh, Tahoe on the Nevada side, Incline
Village, Jackson Hole, Zurich, the Swiss
Alps, any of the places I have
residences, they all love Helix, the
beds.
Somebody will say to me on my Montana
ranch, "What about these beds? What kind
of beds? I say it's Helix.
The Helix Midnight Deluxe is my
favorite, but there's lots of great
ones. You take a short quiz. They tell
you what kind of sleeper are you.
It's really wild what you can learn from
that quiz. I took that quiz. They said I
died three years ago. But they will tell
you what kind of sleeper.
They said, "I'm just living in this
space between life and death, waiting to
be admitted to either eternal glory or
the netherworld." I'm like, "Hold on. I
just said I sleep on my left." But but
my point is, you take the test and then
they tell you what you need. Go to
helixleep.comtimd
for the July sale June 13th, 2025.
And then to be determined, so just take
advantage of this immediately. 25 27%
off sitewide. This is exclusive for the
listeners of the Tim Dylan podcast. I
will tell you this, I've advertised a
lot of products on the show. There's not
one product that people have actually
used more than Helix with me and have
literally came to me and said this is
the best bet ever. So, listeners to the
Tim Dylan podcast, 27% off sitewide. We
do thank Helix for this. Helixleep.comd.
How $29 sandwiches push New York to
socialism. Soaring costs of live, vag
unaffordable rent have fueled the rise
of Okay. Yeah, we don't even need to
read it. I get it. 29 for a ham and
cheese.
That's [__] up.
Best sandwich in New York. You go to My
Hero in
I think it's Belmore or Merrick. Doesn't
matter. It's one of them. North Belmore,
whatever. Get the chicken club. Add
American cheese.
Ki,
which is an app I actually use now.
That's actually kind of fun. You can
come up with your own betting like who
will be the NYC mayoral race winner
because by the way there's a lot of big
money that hate the Zoron guy. So
there's a lot of guys like Bill Aman. A
lot of these guys who put Trump in a lot
of big wealthy NYC donors are like let's
dump Zoron
and replace him with someone else. Now,
that doesn't mean they could prevent him
from running, but
by the way, how impressive and fun would
it be if he just showed up in two like
if he won and came out with a yamaga and
went just kidding.
It would be sick if Zoron came out with
one of those big furry hats, the
Shrimal, and it's just all these acidic
guys. They all started dancing and
Zoron's like, "Gotcha, bitch." It would
just be insane. That's what I'm talking
about. Fun. You know what I mean? Like
that's what it's lacking. Fun like
twists and turns. Like a good show.
Just get Jewish music up. Just find some
non-copyrighted Jewish music. Good luck
with that, by the way. But find find
some non find some non-copyrighted
Jewish for this mammi bit.
Okay. Royalty-free Jewish music. By the
way, I feel like we're somehow still
going to get sued. But
Mami and his wife come out. They just
wave Israeli flags. They're like, "Just
kidding, [__]
You believe the whole Muslim thing? What
are you nuts?"
They're like, he goes, "I only said I
wouldn't visit Israel cuz I'm there
right now." and they're all just dancing
in Tel Aviv and he's like it's mom damia
witz [__]
and then you'd have to hand them and you
say you're good you got me you got me
but
on Khi right now they do have a uh uh
NYC mayoral race winner who will it be
Eric Adams well I lie because he's just
doing blow in clubs
which is what a mayor of New York should
be doing. Should just be staying out of
the fray.
Staying out of the fray.
I want a guy just doing cocaine and
nightclubs. I don't need you talking
about the Middle East.
Eric Adams is concerned with the price
of drugs in America
that he's taking.
So the Kshi Kalhi
markets here, Eric Adams is at 20%,
Cuomo's at seven, and the official
Democratic nominee is Zoron at 72.
Heavily favor Zoron. And I like to play
around with this website every now and
then. You can make a little money, a
little scratch.
Can make a little money, a little
scratch here. I don't always [__] around
with it.
But it is fun.
I'll tell you that much.
It is so catchy. And it's similar to the
Muslim music. The Muslim music is a
little more like
they're just desert peoples. All All of
them. It's interesting. We're not We're
different people. America's like a
different thing.
You know what I mean? America's kind of
like
it's a different thing, but they're very
so it's like figuring out a way for all
that to work is like so hard. It's hard.
It's hard.
Go get up this rapist.
I'm defending this man. How dare people
look at this man. Norwegian Prince
Marius Borg Hoy,
28, charged with three rapes amid slew
of allegations against disgrace royal.
Look at this man. Does that guy seem
like he'd rape three people?
A Norwegian prince has been charged with
three rapes among a slew of sex and
violence allegations involving a
double-digit number of alleged victims.
He looks so nice. Look at him. Get him
up. Look at that guy. Does that man seem
like he would just walk around
sexually assaulting everyone?
I mean, he does have he's he's like the
most evil guy I've ever seen.
Yeah, he's a bad guy.
He's a bad dude. Marius Borg Hoy, what
country is this? I just said it. What is
this? Norway? Yeah, Norway.
He's He's a bad man.
Corey Monty's mom and dad died 12 years
after Glee stars
tragic death. You know that Glee thing.
You ever want to be depressed? Watch
that documentary.
They all get selected for the show and
then all of them one of them's a
pedophile. Everyone else kills himself.
Someone dies in a lake. It's Final
Destination Glee. It's tough. It's sad.
He's also accused of raping. I can't
keep saying that word. They're going to
get so mad at us on this YouTube
unconscious TV star Lenny Meister, 39,
at one of his wild scalgum festival
parties allegedly held in the basement
of the royal estate.
So, he had these parties at the basement
And he released a statement saying he
suffers from several mental disorders
and has struggled with substance abuse
for a long time. It read, "Last weekend
something happened that should never
have happened. and I committed bodily
harm and destroyed objects in an
apartment in the intoxication of alcohol
and cocaine after an argument. I've
struggled with substance abuse for a
long time, something I've been in
treatment for in the past. The drug use
and my diagnosis is do not excuse what
happened in the apartment at Frogner on
the night of Sunday last week. I want to
be responsible for what I've done and
will explain myself truthfully
truthfully to the police.
Here's the way it all works over there.
And I'm going to just tell everybody so
that there's no confusion.
They all have these castles
and
during the day they'll do like, "Hey,
come on over. We're doing a thing."
So people go over and they got a little
Swedish meatball or red cabbage. Red
cabbage is good and you don't get it
enough as a side. Why can't I have it?
It's not with the beets. Red cabbage is
good. So they're doing stuff like that,
right? They go, "Hey, come on out. We're
doing a castle. We got red cabbage, a
little noodle dish, maybe some schnit
little schnitle.
You go over there, you have a beer. You
have a beer. A beer.
And you eat and it's nice. And then they
send you home and you go,
whatever." like some type of you know
and I'm talking about all of them over
there Belgium the whole gang Germany
Norway Scandinav all these with the
European royalty Scandinavian all this
stuff right
and then I'm telling you I'm not this is
the way it is then like an old woman
comes out they like wheel her out and
she's like sitting on the
like on the the steps of the palace and
she's
It is time.
And then they release
like uh um all of some of the workers
or and the children are forced to strip
naked and run through the woods and then
the elite people hunt them. And when
they find them, they have sex with them
and kill them. and the old woman and
some of the older people watch because
they can no longer run after the people.
So sometimes somebody will be brought to
them to have sex with her and say,
"Okay, you can eat this one.
We got we caught it for you."
But they're watching this whole thing
and they remember like when we were
young we would run after the children
and the you know the help the helpers
and and then we would um rape uh and
kill them and then they light them on
fire and everything. They do druid pagan
rituals. So he grew up in that.
Not to excuse his behavior,
but like he grew up in that system where
they're like it's
it's the death. It's the But here's the
thing that those people had. They had a
little discipline. They had a little
discipline. He's just raping any old
person he sees. That's not the game. The
game is there's an organized human hunt
where we let people run through the
forest and then chase after them and
kill them and eat them and rape them.
And by the way, if you think I'm lying,
Google this. It's true. And it probably
still goes on. Why wouldn't it? And
actually, as much as I might disagree
with it, I see actually a huge benefit
to tradition, especi specifically
European tradition. Not to be racist,
but you have people, not to be like like
a crazy person,
but they have human hunts on the grounds
of these castles, and it's well
organized, and they, you know, some
people disappear from the town. It
happens once a year, a couple of times a
year. It's it's festival. It's like an
autoutuminal one. And it's f. So this
kid's raised in that. And then
he starts doing all this stuff. His
parents go, "You can't act like this."
And he goes, "Well, what about the human
hunt?" When I was four, you know, you
guys were, you know, you're having sex
with people in front of me, killing
them, cannibalizing them. It's like,
that's a holiday. That's what has to be
explained to these kids. It's a holiday.
You know, we would as kids go, "Why
can't we have Easter candy?" That's a
holiday. Oh, but we we Yeah, you don't
get it every day. Halloween, you don't
get it every day. It's a holiday. So,
when European royalty hunts humans on
the grounds of their castle, rapes,
tortures, burns them, and eats them. You
don't They have to make it understood
that their kids like, "Buddy, we fought
wars to do this, okay? We're actually
sacrificing people to pagan gods. We
have a relationship with the demonic and
that we're upholding some sort of uh
pact or agreement with and we fought
years and years and years to be able to
a few days out of the year relax and do
a human hunt.
But these are special moments for us.
There's actually a lot of pageantry and
ceremony involved. You're just out there
willy-nilly
raping people in the dorm room. That
ain't the way it works, buddy.
So he said, "Whoa, what about the human
hunt?" And they're like, "It's the
that's a holiday." His father says, the
king, "That's a holiday. And that's
between us.
The human hunt or they call it the hunt.
The hunt
is actually something very special.
You know how sad your grandmother's
going to be when she reads these
allegations.
But grandma watches us all rape and eat
the children. Yes, of course. On a
holiday.
The fact that you're behaving like this
and bringing shame to our family
because all of these royal fam in
Europe, it's just what goes on. It's not
even a big deal. And the people know it.
The people know it.
Some people go, "Yeah, it's hunt
weekend. Don't be stupid." They know it.
The people It's It's boring. Oh, yeah.
You're gonna hunt a couple of people,
chop them up. We get it.
These royals now, they don't even have
any power in these countries. The EU's
taken over. They flood them all with
immigrants. Everyone loses their minds.
And the royals have nothing except the
hunt.
and it's the only time they feel
powerful.
So, is that a good idea to move on from
monarchy to have all these super
national institutions like the EU? So,
we've moved away from these bloodthirsty
pagan royal bloodlines and replace them
with bureaucrats in Brussels
and these people sit in their castles.
They're bored as [__] They don't want
to go to the opening of a new hospital.
They want the hunt.
But their children need to understand
that the hunt is a special occasion.
It's not all the time. So this prince,
what's his name again? Hoy. What's his
name?
Hoy. Go up. Get his name.
What is it? Bjorn.
Marius. Marius. Borg. Hoy.
Marius. Please behave and wait till the
hunt.
It's actually nicer if you wait till the
My father told me once, I said to him,
we're on the way to a swim meet and I
said, "Dad, can I get McDonald's?" And
he said, "Son, a hungry dog runs the
furthest." Runs the farthest. A hungry
dog runs the farthest. So, Marius, a
hungry dog runs the farthest. Wait till
the hunt. Have your fun on the hunt and
then get nuts. Rip people's intestines
out with your teeth. I mean, really go
on a bender, but don't ruin it with
these little snacks. Don't ruin the meal
with a snack.
Don't ruin the meal
with a snack. to our most mo to our
maybe new mayor
ISIS
Bin Laden
Omar.
I wish him well. I wish him the best of
luck. I I love New York City.
Uh yes, but I also hate a lot of people
who live here, but I also love people
who live here. But I could, it's a great
narrative either way. Whether it
succeeds or is completely destroyed,
it's actually a good narrative for me
either way. I don't care. Um, if it
succeeds, I will enjoy it. If it fails
miserably, I will move and just talk
about it. Really, with me, it's six of
one, half a dozen of the other, isn't
it?
So, in closing, we've learned a lot
today, and I think we've balanced
ourselves in a healthy way. We can't
expect old dogs to learn new tricks.
But sometimes, like Andrew Cuomo, we got
to take him to the shelter, put him
down, put a needle in that old pup,
and watch him fade away.
That's right. We've learned that people
that have made uh uh uh you know bad
choices with uh how much money they've
taken out in student loans
and are living in uh cities like New
York are unhappy because they were told
that they deserved more in life. I am
here to tell them uh you do not. You
actually do not. And I've always been
here to tell them that you do not. You
are normies. You are nothing.
That is what you are. Find me a Brooklyn
hipster or whoever the people are. I'll
find you the most normal suburban basic
[__] in the world. That's all you are.
You could dress it up any which way you
like.
That being said, I wish uh Zoron well
because I love the city and I want to
see it thrive and want to succeed. I
wish Donald Trump well. I'd like to not
get involved with the Iran. It doesn't
seem like we are.
At the end of the day, you have to find
things in your life that make you happy
outside of political rage.
I know that it powers most of us. Just
being angry all the time at things, but
there's a lot of other emotions instead
of being angry. Like jealousy
can do that.
coveting, being envious,
but the class war is coming.
Fundamentally, it is.
The the lesson here is that the future
of American politics is going to be
written by two opposing versions of
populism.
one that concentrates its eye and rage
on a set of financial elites
and people in the government they feel
have sold out to them.
Um and then the other type of populism
will be doing that as well. But they
will also include cultural elites who
they feel have worked in concert with
the financial elites to destroy the
cultural foundations of society, further
impoverishing people, making them
helpless and driving them into
desperation and pathological behavior.
I
will be on the hunt
in Belgium in that famous castle that I
read about
and they will go,
"It is time for the hunt." And the old
woman will come out. I will be the only
one who the the the um the people that
were hunting run faster than me. So,
it's gonna be embarrassing that I like I
keep
and even the old woman's like, "He keeps
falling down. Will someone kill a
peasant and bring them to him?" I'm
like, "No, let me try. Let me try the
hunt."
But
American politics now,
the peasants of the village
actually have turned
and they are hunting
the elites of the castle. And so the
elites of the castle have split into two
factions and they're standing on two
balconies trying to convince the
peasants that the hunt was actually the
other party's idea.
What happens now, we don't know. Good
luck. Happy hunting.